zeably.com 2012-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Zeably

This statement describes our privacy policy. Zeably reserves the right to revise this policy at any time without notification to you, so please re-read it often in connection with your use of the Zeably.com and related domains and websites.

Zeably respects your right to privacy. We understand the sensitive nature of privacy issues and the company takes measures to ensure that the confidentiality of our clients and web users is protected. Zeably does not distribute, sell, or rent any of the information collected about our website users or clients.

Zeably does not and will never rent, sell or share information that personally identifies you for marketing purposes without your express permission. No email content or other personally identifiable information will be provided to advertisers.

**Third-Party Content**

Zeably aggregates third party content, by retrieving original web content from third party services, displaying these contents inside a webpage. These results sites are owned and maintained by independent companies, over which Zeably has no control, and who are not covered by this privacy policy. Zeably is not responsible or liable for the content of these sites, or their collection of information and its use. If you have any concerns about your privacy at one of these sites, please review their sites' policies or contact them directly.

**Links to Other Sites**

As a provider of advertising and publisher services, you will find various links on our sites and clients' sites, including but not limited to: Sponsored Listings, Zeably' Partners, banners, pops, interstitials, etc. The sites these all link to are owned and maintained by independent companies, over which Zeably has no control, and who are not covered by this privacy policy. Zeably is not responsible or liable for the content of these sites, or their collection of information and its use. If you have any concerns about your privacy at one of these sites, please review their sites' policies or contact them directly.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Cookies and web beacons are small files that are downloaded to your computer, and that allow Zeably to collect aggregate statistical information. They are not in any way harmful to your computer, nor are they capable of personally identifying you. Rather, they are only capable of collecting anonymous information, and letting us know basic information about your visit.

**Information Collected**

By using Zeably.com or any of its domains and websites, you will be providing Zeably with certain limited anonymous information, based on your activities. This information cannot be traced back to you, or matched up to personally identifying information in any way - it is completely anonymous, and will only be used in aggregate form with the information collected from other site visitors. Should you choose to correspond with, or participate in any of Zeably' services or products, however, you will be asked to provide personally identifiable information, in order that we may respond, or [do business in China](http://www.china-window.com/china_business/doing_business_in_china/index.shtml) with you. Please see below for more details on the kinds of anonymous and identifiable information Zeably collects.

ANONYMOUS: When a user visits Zeably.com, they leave a "trail" of electronic information, which is collected and stored on our servers. This information, often referred to as traffic, or click-stream, data is not personally identifiable nor is it possible to combine with any kind of identifiable information we may collect from you by other means (see Personally Identifiable Information, below). Rather, click-stream data consists of very limited and specific information about your computer, your browser, and its activities. For example: your computer's IP address, its operating system, the type and version of your browser, the date and time, the length of time spent on each page, search terms, results or advertisements clicked upon, and referral data.

This anonymous information is used to monitor our traffic and servers, as well as to screen for fraudulent behavior or abnormalities. It is also used to compile statistics and perform research by analyzing it in aggregate form, which in turn helps us to improve our services and offerings to both users of our sites and services.

PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION: In certain limited circumstances, Zeably may gain access to your personally identifiable information. This information is made available to Zeably voluntarily, when a user or potential client specifically and knowingly provides it to us, in order to correspond with us, or to receive a service they've requested.

1\. Correspondence: When a site user or potential client gives comments, questions, information requests, or feedback to Zeably by phone, mail, or email (either directly or through one of our online forms) and includes an email address and/or contact information, Zeably will use this information in order to respond. The contact information provided, however, is not stored in any kind of database. It is only maintained as a record of past correspondence, either in the responders' files or sent items in their email software.

2\. Special Offers: When you participate in special offers, contests, or surveys, the collection of contact information is often required for registration, and for winner notification. In some instances, these are co-sponsored and so your information will be shared with that particular partner.

Please note, that some contests or services advertised on or through Zeably, by either search or graphic advertisers, may require personal contact information in order to enter or register. This information is not shared with Zeably, and these advertisers are not covered by this privacy policy (please see Links to Other Sites, above) although they may adhere to their own similar policies.

3\. Registration/Application for Services: Advertisers or site owners who wish to advertise through Zeably will be requested to provide personally identifiable and financial information in order to participate in these programs. The collection of this information is part of regular business practices and is necessary in order to complete transactions and properly run and administer these services. Should anyone be uncomfortable providing this information to Zeably, they can choose not to participate.

Information collected during the registration or application processes, include: company name, name, email, physical address, and phone number. Advertisers may also be asked to provide credit card information in order to process and authorize payments to Zeably for services rendered, and publishers may be asked to provide either their Social Security Number or Federal Tax ID Number in order to receive payments for impressions or clicks delivered on their sites. Overall, personally identifiable information of Zeably clients is used for administrative needs, to maintain account information, and to process billing and payments.

**Unsolicited Contact & Communication**

Zeably will not sell, rent, or disclose any of the contact information we have collected from you to third parties, except as described in this document (see Special Offers, above and Information Sharing, below).

We, however, may occasionally wish to communicate with our customers in order to provide them with information relevant to the services we provide or the management of their accounts. This might include newsletters, or notices of new services or offers from Zeably or selected partners that could be of interest. In addition, we will provide clients with their initial activation and welcome email, service and system updates, account and balance warnings, confirmation emails, and quality approval notifications.

As part of our service, our Customer Service Department routinely communicates with members by phone or email to respond to questions or issues relating to their account, or to offer optimization services. We may also solicit some of our clients from time to time, either online or by email, to participate in client surveys. Participation in these surveys is voluntary, and the information collected provides Zeably with valuable feedback on our services, which in turn, helps us to improve them.

**Information Sharing**

Zeably may share the information we gather from cookies, web beacons, survey respondents, etc., with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other selected third parties. This sharing of information is done only in an aggregate form for statistical purposes.

Your personally identifiable information, submitted during your registration or application, is shared only with third party companies who provide Zeably with administrative services required to conduct [china business](http://www.china-window.com/china_business/) with our clients and provide them with the services they have signed up for. Examples include: technical consultants; third-party credit card processing; credit checks; money transfers and auditing. Under no circumstances do these service partners or Zeably disclose any of your personally identifiable information, unless we are obligated to do so by law (due to a court order, subpoena, etc), or to protect Zeably, our users, or the general public.

Zeably may identify some of our clients as current or past advertisers or publishers on gallery pages on the Zeably website. Identification of our clients will be in the form of their business identity, or brand, only.

**Security**

Any data collected and stored on Zeably' servers is considered proprietary and confidential, and is not available to the public. We have security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of user and customer data under our control. As data security is constantly evolving, we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of the data will not occur, but will do our utmost to prevent against any such occurrences.

Clients' personally identifiable information is password protected and restricted within our organization to employees that need access to this information in order to correspond with you, operate the website or a particular service.

**Children Under 13 Years of Age**

In light of the concern over protecting children's privacy online, Zeably. does not knowingly request, collect, or share personally identifiable information from users under the age of 13. Our websites, products and services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children.
